A funny movie about getting serious.
Crossing Delancey is a comedy, romance film directed by Joan Micklin Silver.
Thirty-something Isabelle spends her time going from her tiny, solitary West
Side apartment to that of her grandmother on the Lower East Side.
While her grandmother plots to find her a romantic match, Isabelle is courted by a married, worldly
author, Anton, yet can't seem to shake the down-to-earth appeal of Sam, a pickle vendor.
Isabelle Grossman, played by Amy Irving.
Sam Posner, played by Peter Riegert.
Bubbie Kantor, played by Reizl Bozyk.
Anton Maes, played by Jeroen Krabbé.
Hannah Mandelbaum, played by Sylvia Miles.
Lionel, played by George Martin.
Crossing Delancey is a 1988 American romantic comedy film adapted by  Susan Sandler
from her play of the same name, and directed by Joan Micklin Silver.
It stars Amy Irving and Peter Riegert.
The film also features performances from Reizl Bozyk, David
Hyde-Pierce, Sylvia Miles and Rosemary Harris.
Amy Irving was nominated for a Golden Globe for the film, for Best
Actress in a Motion Picture - Comedy or Musical.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.